=Ex-Wife Stop Ⅱ=
= توقف الزوجة السابقة Ⅱ =
=Episode 4=
= الحلقة 4 =
I don't celebrate birthdays. Get out.
أنا لا أحتفل بأعياد الميلاد.  اخرج.
(Sheng Nanfang.)
(شنغ نانفانغ.)
(Do you know Yan did many things)
(هل تعلم أن يان فعل أشياء كثيرة)
(just to let you restore your memory?)
(فقط للسماح لك باستعادة ذاكرتك؟)
(She's under so much pressure at work,)
(إنها تحت ضغط شديد في العمل ،)
(and you gave her that look at home.)
(وأعطيتها ذلك النظرة إلى المنزل).
I didn't mean to do that yesterday.
لم أقصد أن أفعل ذلك بالأمس.
(It was not her fault that you got hurt and lost your memory.)
(لم يكن ذنبها أنك جرحت وفقدت ذاكرتك).
(You're so ungrateful.)
(أنت جاحد جدا.)
(You bad man.)
(أنت رجل سيء.)
Mr. Sheng.
السيد شنغ.
The gift you asked for is ready.
الهدية التي طلبتها جاهزة.
Is it an appropriate apology gift?
هل هي هدية اعتذار مناسبة؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
A girl will stop being angry
الفتاة ستتوقف عن الغضب
when she sees such a big diamond.
عندما ترى مثل هذا الماس الكبير.
Now the share price of Sheng Group is low.
الآن سعر سهم Sheng Group منخفض.
It is indeed the best time to acquire it.
إنه بالفعل أفضل وقت للحصول عليه.
The previous acquisitions were just small attempts.
كانت عمليات الاستحواذ السابقة مجرد محاولات صغيرة.
If I want to be recognized,
إذا أردت أن يتم التعرف علي ،
the best way is to snap up Sheng Group.
أفضل طريقة هي اقتناص مجموعة Sheng.
You're right,
أنت على حق،
but I don't want to do this.
لكني لا أريد أن أفعل هذا.
Nanfang has put tremendous effort into Sheng Group.
لقد بذل Nanfang جهودًا هائلة في Sheng Group.
I don't want to take advantage of that.
لا أريد الاستفادة من ذلك.
I can prove myself without acquiring the group.
يمكنني إثبات نفسي دون اكتساب المجموعة.
(Mr. Li) (Crescent will go home.)
(السيد لي) (سيعود الهلال إلى المنزل).
Zhao Xian.
تشاو زيان.
Check out the Hechuan project,
تحقق من مشروع Hechuan ،
and try to find out if anyone is behind our back.
ونحاول معرفة ما إذا كان هناك من يقف وراء ظهورنا.
Go check especially
اذهب للتحقق خاصة
if Tianqi Group is involved.
إذا كانت مجموعة Tianqi متورطة.
As soon as possible.
في أسرع وقت ممكن.
Little bug,
حشرة صغيرة،
- can you not come here? - Crescent,
- ألا يمكنك المجيء إلى هنا؟  - هلال،
you have to keep an eye on that bug,
عليك أن تراقب هذا الخطأ ،
and don't let it get out.
ولا تدعها تخرج.
If it gets out, I'll catch it back.
إذا خرج ، سألتقطه مرة أخرى.
Fine.
بخير.
I won't stop you,
لن اوقفك
but you'll have to say something nice about me
لكن عليك أن تقول شيئًا لطيفًا عني
in front of your dad tonight.
أمام والدك الليلة.
No way.
مستحيل.
Take your time.
خذ وقتك.
Don't I often cook for you?
لا أطبخ لك كثيرًا؟
You seldom cook.
نادرا ما تطبخ.
Of course I want to eat more.
بالطبع أريد أن آكل أكثر.
Mom, what are you doing?
أمي ماذا تفعلين؟
Dad.
أب.
Me?
أنا؟
Yeah.
نعم.
Is the lantern done?
هل تم الانتهاء من الفانوس؟
What lantern?
أي فانوس؟
It's for my craft class.
إنه لفصلي الحرفية.
Really?
حقًا؟
You don't forget it, do you?
لا تنسى ذلك ، أليس كذلك؟
It's due tomorrow.
إنه مستحق غدا.
I-I-I'll do it right away.
II- سأفعل ذلك على الفور.
I love you, Dad.
أحبك أبي.
You are such a good father.
أنت أب جيد.
Don't get me wrong.
لا تفهموني خطأ.
It is just because I'm honest and trustworthy.
هذا فقط لأنني صادق وجدير بالثقة.
Okay.
تمام.
Go for it.
أذهب خلفها.
I'll get you some picture books for reference.
سأحضر لك بعض الكتب المصورة كمرجع.
- I didn't mean to.
- لم أقصد ذلك.  - لم أقصد ذلك.
I-I-I'm going to check on Crescent.
II- سأقوم بفحص الهلال.
How did that happen?
كيف حدث هذا؟
Wait. Why am I nervous?
انتظر.  لماذا انا متوتر؟
Didn't we kiss a lot?
ألم نقبل كثيرا؟
♪The waves get close to your body♪
الأمواج تقترب من جسمك ♪
♪In the blazing sun♪
في الشمس الحارقة
♪I'm close to you♪
♪ أنا قريب منك ♪
♪Close to the sea♪
♪ قريب من البحر ♪
This man. He should hide it well.
هذا الرجل.  يجب أن يخفيه جيداً.
♪The romance and enthusiasm conveyed by your hair♪
الرومانسية والحماس الذي ينقله شعرك
♪The intimacy in your eyes♪
الحميمية في عينيك ♪
♪On a six-inch screen♪
♪ على شاشة ست بوصات ♪
♪The corners of my mouth look like meniscus♪
زوايا فمي تشبه الغضروف المفصلي ♪
♪I hug you. You raise your arms♪
♪ أنا أحضنك.  ترفع ذراعيك ♪
♪It's the summer I'm looking forward to♪
♪ إنه الصيف الذي أتطلع إليه ♪
♪My mood changes with the weather and your mood♪
♪ يتغير مزاجي مع الطقس ومزاجك ♪
♪I caress you in the clear dawn♪
أعانقك في الفجر الصافي
♪It's the summer I love and hate♪
♪ إنه الصيف الذي أحبه وأكره
♪Against the wind, I come near you, around you♪
v مقابل الريح اقترب منك حولك
♪In this noisy world, I only think of you♪
♪ في هذا العالم الصاخب ، أفكر فيك فقط
♪Wow♪
♪ واو ♪
♪It's the summer I love and hate♪
♪ إنه الصيف الذي أحبه وأكره
♪I hold you. I walk close to you♪
♪ أنا أمسك بك.  أمشي بالقرب منك ♪
♪I look at you in the cool evening breeze♪
أنظر إليك في نسيم المساء البارد
♪You are the hope. You are the purpose♪
♪ أنت الأمل.  أنت الغرض ♪
♪You're the sweet taste I can't resist♪
♪ أنت الذوق الحلو الذي لا يمكنني مقاومته ♪
♪All my summer dreams are about you♪
♪ كل أحلامي الصيفية عنك